(Howard:)and let them listen
to the music of their homeland.
I need to tinkle!
Sounds like the job
for a loving person.
Would you liko me to play Polish music
while you carry her to the toilet?
(Bernadette:)You are a putz.
(Howard:)As advertised.
(Sheldon:)Thanks for coming with me.
(Raj:)Thanks for inviting me
after everyone else said no.
(Raj:)Aren't you gonna get 3-D glasses?
(Sheldon:)I brought my own.
(Sheldon:)No sense in risking
bridge-of-nose herpes.
(Raj:)Is that a real thing?
(Sheldon:)Well, until they invent
nose condoms, I'm not finding out.
Emily! Hey!
(Emily:)Oh, hey, Raj.
(Raj:)This is my friend, Sheldon.
Sheldon, this is Emily.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, you're the dermatologist.